RESUME Last updated: 14.04.2024



3D DEVELOPER

INDUSTRY

Fitness Retail Customer care

ORGANISATION

B2C International/Swedish English/Swedish

SYSTEM

Blender
Autodesk Maya
Unity
Substance Painter
Adobe Photoshop
Pro Tools
Logic Pro X
Visual Studio Code

PLATFORM

Desktop/Mobile Web/Native

SKILLS

Swedish, native English, fluent Class B Driving License Certified User Pro Tools Programming 1 C#

SARA JOHNSSON

Phone: +46 (0) 709 56 06 28 | **E-mail:** saraisabelljohnsson@gmail.com |

Website: sjohnsson.wixsite.com/portfolio

ABOUT

Sara is an ambitious and driven 3D-developer with a passion for the visual arts. By utilizing her knowledge in VR/AR development, sound and music production as well as customer service she aims to integrate the different experiences to create dynamic and engaging projects. With a diverse background encompassing various fields, she enjoys embracing new challenges and continually expanding her skill set.

ASSIGNMENTS

Promenad | DVA | Apr 2022-Jun 2022

The assignment was to create 3D-assets and animations suited for augmented reality for the application 'Promenad' that involved two different projects. 'Stockholm Möts' takes the audience along an interactive audio walk with elements of augmented reality that leads you through the streets and squares of the capital. The story revolves around human encounters that provide a unique

the capital. The story revolves around human encounters that provide a unique perspective of Stockholm's history and the important place of LGBTQ culture in it.

'Manufacture and for the city of Halsinghers to showere a exciting stories of the control of the city of Halsinghers to showere a exciting stories of the city of Halsinghers to showere a exciting stories.

'Monument' was made for the city of Helsingborg to showcase exciting stories of the city's inhabitants. Along the way, some of their monument suggestions come to life as part of the experience through your mobile phone.

Blender, Unity

Shell | DVA | Apr 2022-Jun 2022

The assignment was to UV-map and occlusion bake provided 3D-models for Shell to be able to visualise their factory.

Blender, WebGL

Real Estate VR | Fernandez Design Sweden | Nov 2020-Jan 2021

The assignment was to visualise an apartment in Spain before it was renovated. The goal was to create an immersive experience for customers before they invest in the property, with functionalities such as being able to walk around in a full scale environment. This included building the entire apartment in 3D as well as generating textures and baking lights for the environment. Autodesk Maya, Unity, C#

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Agent | Addnature

Dec 2022-Apr 2024

Shop Assistant | Media Markt

Jul 2021-Dec 2022

Personal Trainer | SATS Sports Club Sep 2017-Dec 2018

VR Game | Hello World | Aug 2020-Nov 2020

In collaboration with the organisation Hello World, the assignment was to create two different games about the 13 Sustainable Development Goals by the UN to be used at different exhibitions. The objective was to create an experience that involved both user and audience to solve the in-game task together. Autodesk Maya, Unity, C#, FMod

Fluorescence Detection | Cybercom Group | Mar 2020-Apr 2020

The purpose of this assignment was to create an educational application connected to a testing instrument, to show the amount of algae in a tube of water. By using the device in virtual reality, the user will learn how the application and test instrument works before using it in the field.

Autodesk Maya, Unity, C#

EDUCATION

VR/AR Development | Nackademin Jan 2019-Jan 2021

B.A Sound and music production | University of Dalama Aug 2014-Jun 2017

Lic. Personal Trainer | SAFE Education Jun 2017-Aug 2017